pizzahut.com 2009-06-06

# PizzaHut.com — Privacy Policy

Pizza Hut, Inc. (hereinafter referred to as either, "Company", "We", "Us" or "Our") is committed to protecting the privacy of personal information you may provide Us on this website (the “Site”). We believe it is important for you to know how We treat your personal information. We updated this Privacy Policy effective as of November 12, 2008. The terms of this Privacy Policy apply to all users of this Site. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, you should immediately cease the use of this Site. Below you will find answers to several questions regarding Our revised Privacy Policy. 

  * What information does Company collect about me on this Site?  

  * What does Company do with the information collected?  

  * With whom does Company share the information?  

  * How can I stop receiving notices about future offers or to stop my Personal Information from being shared with third parties?  

  * How do I correct or update my Personal Information?  

  * How does Company protect the security of my Personal Information?  

  * Does Company's Site link to other sites?  

  * What is the effective date of Company Privacy Policy and how will Company notify me of changes to its Privacy Policy?  

  * How does Company handle children's privacy online?  

  * How do I contact Company?

## 

Company collects personally identifiable information that you may voluntarily provide on online forms, which may include: user registration, sweepstakes registration, contact requests, guest comments, online surveys, and other online activities. The personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) collected on this Site can include some or all of the following: your name, address, telephone number(s), e-mail addresses, text messaging information and other contact information associated with electronic or digital messaging methods, vehicles and interaction, credit card information, demographic information, and any other information you may voluntarily provide. You will have the choice whether or not to disclose such Personal Information in the above activities; however, some parts of the Site and some services may be more difficult or impossible to use if you choose not to disclose Personal Information. 

At the time of registration, you will have the option to receive future offers and updates from the Company by checking the appropriate opt-in box(es). If you choose to opt-in, your Personal Information will be kept in a secured database and We will alert you via your selected opt-in communication method (i.e., e-mail, text messaging, etc.) to new features, special offers, updated information and new services. 

In addition to the Personal Information identified above, Our web servers automatically identify computers by their IP addresses. Company may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. To emphasize, IP addresses are not linked to Personal Information. 

Further, Our Site may use technologies such as “cookies” to provide visitors with tailored information upon each visit. Cookies are a common part of many commercial websites that allow small text files to be sent by a website, accepted by a web browser and then placed on your hard drive as recognition for repeat visits to the Site. Every time you visit Our Site, Our servers, through cookies, pixels and/or GIF files, collect basic technical information such as your domain name, the address of the last URL visited prior to clicking through to the Site, and your browser and operating system. You do not need to enable cookies to visit Our Site; however, some parts of the Site and some services may be more difficult or impossible to use if cookies are disabled. To emphasize, cookies are not linked to any Personal Information while on this Site. 

Company's ad management partner, Microsoft Advertiser & Publisher Solutions (Atlas), employs pixels or transparent GIF files to help manage Our online advertising. These files enable Atlas to recognize a unique cookie on your web browser, which in turn enables Us to learn which advertisements bring users to Our website. The cookie was placed by Us, or by another advertiser who works with Atlas. With both cookies and Universal Action Tag technology, the information We collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number(s), or email address. For more information about Atlas, including information on how to opt out of these technologies, go to <http://www.atlassolutions.com/privacy>. 

## 

Company may use your Personal Information for any of the following purposes: (1) to understand the use of the Site and make improvements; (2) to fulfill prizes; (3) to register visitors for online activities such as: online ordering, sweepstakes, contests, surveys, employment applications, comment forms, or any other online interactive activities; (4) to respond to specific requests from visitors; (5) to obtain parental consent from visitors under 18 years of age, when necessary; (6) to provide any necessary notices to visitors or their parent or legal guardians if situations prompt such notification; (7) to protect the security or integrity of the Site if necessary; (8) to send notices of special promotions, offers or solicitations through your selected opt-in methods; and (9) in general, to promote and market Company's business and various products. 

In addition, from time to time, We may market certain third party services through Our Site. Should you choose to accept an offer from a third party, We will pass your relevant Personal Information, which may include your name, address, and credit/debit card number, to that third party. 

## 

Company is a part of [Yum! Brands, Inc](http://www.yum.com/privacy.asp). ("Yum Brands"). Yum Brands includes: [KFC U.S. Properties, Inc.](http://www.kfc.com/privacy.asp), [Taco Bell Corp.](http://www.tacobell.com/legal/privacypolicy.html), Pizza Hut, Inc., [Long John Silver's, Inc.](http://www.ljsilvers.com/privacy/), [A&W Restaurants, Inc.](http://www.awrestaurants.com/footercontent/privacy.asp), and [Yum Restaurants International, Inc](http://www.yrigfp.com/legal.asp). Company may share Personal Information collected on this Site with any member of Yum Brands, its franchisees, and any other future subsidiaries or affiliates. This Privacy Policy applies if Company shares your Personal Information collected on this Site with any other Yum Brands members. If you choose to provide your Personal Information to other members of Yum Brands through their respective websites, then the respective Privacy Policies will apply. 

Company will not sell, rent, loan, transfer, or otherwise disclose any Personal Information to third parties except as set forth in this statement. Company may share Personal Information with third parties under the following circumstances: (i) in connection with a court order, subpoena, government investigation, or when otherwise required by law; (ii) in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, or similar event; or (iii) working with third party companies to support the Site's technical operation or execute a specific promotion or program (such as providing responses to the Guest Comments Page, conduct surveys, or maintain a database of visitor information, etc.); or (iv) to facilitate your transactions with Our third party marketing partners. 

If Personal Information is shared with any third party for the purposes of executing a specific promotion or program, it will be clearly communicated to visitors that the third party will have no right to use the Personal Information for independent purposes without your consent. In support of this policy, Company will enter into written agreements with any third party receiving Personal Information requiring the third party to comply with Company's privacy policies and applicable laws. To avoid your Personal Information from being shared with a third party, you can choose not to use the affected service or participate in the affected promotional activity. 

## 

For those who initially opted-in to receive future offers or promotional materials or to allow the sharing of Personal Information with third parties may subsequently opt-out as follows: 

  * For email communications: (a) send an e-mail to [webmaster@pizzahut.com](mailto:webmaster@pizzahut.com) or (b) if you are a registered user, deselect the option on your accounts profile page under "My Account" on Our website;
  * For text message communications, (a) send an email to [webmaster@pizzahut.com](mailto:webmaster@pizzahut.com) and include the appropriate mobile telephone number(s), (b) send a "STOP" text message to "749488" or (c) if you are a registered user, deselect the option on your accounts profile page under "My Account" on Our website.
  * Please understand that if you opt-out, and later accept an offer from an advertiser or one of Our third party marketing partners, We will share your Personal Information with that specific third party.

## 

Those who have registered on Our website may review, correct, update or delete/deactivate their Personal Information, by logging onto Our Site and clicking on “My Account” to make the appropriate changes. 

If you are not a Registered User, you may send an email to [webmaster@pizzahut.com](mailto:webmaster@pizzahut.com) to correct, update or delete/deactivate their applicable email address(es). 

## 

Company uses appropriate security measures to protect all Personal Information collected in a secure, controlled environment. In addition, Company configures the list server software to refuse to divulge the e-mail addresses of the list subscribers to anyone other than authorized Company staff members, including other list subscribers. In the event of a security breach whereas your Personal Information is acquired by an unauthorized person, Company will take appropriate steps to contain the breach and to notify you of the unauthorized acquisition. 

## 

Yes. This Site may contain links to other websites that may not be owned or operated by Company. Company cannot control nor is responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites. Company encourages you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to Personal Information collected on this Site. 

## 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on November 12, 2008. Company will post any changes on the Site's Homepage, so visitors are always aware of any changes to what information We collect, how We use it, and under what circumstances We disclose it. If We decide to use your Personal Information in a manner different than first communicated, Company will notify users by e-mail to the e-mail addresses on record. Users will then be given a choice as to whether or not their Personal Information can be used in the new manner. 

In the event that Company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, another company acquires Company or its Affiliates, or Company sells a portion of its assets, your personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. At least ten days prior to the change of ownership or control, you will be informed of this exchange and its effects via prominent notice on Our site. If as a result of a business transition, your personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, you will be give the choice to opt-out. 

## 

Company adheres to the federal privacy protection standards articulated in the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). 

On the sections of the Site directed towards children, Company does not collect Personal Information online from children under 13 without their parent's consent, except to respond to email as described below. Company may collect information that is not Personal Information in special, limited circumstances, as described below. If a child is under 13 and wants to use the children's sites with special activities, like scavenger hunts, personalized pages or clubs, Company might ask the child to "register" by giving Us a user name and his/her state of residence. When asking for a child's user name, the child is encouraged to use a "screen name" (not his/her real name) that only the child knows. Sometimes the child will be asked to make up a special password so that only they can see their customized areas on the site. 

With parent's verifiable consent, Company may collect personal information from a child such as a full name or an e-mail address when the information is necessary for a particular activity. A parent can provide verifiable consent to Company by printing a permission form that is posted to this Site, signing and returning it to the Webmaster by either (1) mail to 14841 Dallas Parkway, Dallas, Texas 75254 or (2) fax to 972-338-7689. When We ask for parental permission, We will tell the parents what We will do with the information his/her child provides Us, and We will tell parents how they can review their child's information and ask Us to delete the information. We do not keep parents' (or children's) e-mail address unless parents grant Us permission to do so. 

Company might retain and use an email address and any information contained in an email from a child under 13 without the parent's consent, but only in the following special case: If we discover that a child under 13 has sent an email request to Us or has otherwise communicated with us through electronic means (such as through the “Contact Us” portion of the Site), We will keep their e-mail address and the message for long enough to respond to them. In such event, Company may retain the email address and message (both the original message and the response) in its data archives in accordance with Company's data retention policies, but Company will not include the child's information in a marketing database or otherwise use that information for marketing or any purposes in violation of COPPA. 

Occasionally, Company has special site activities or promotions like sweepstakes or contests which are open to children even if they are under 13. In these activities, Company is not allowed to ask for more information from a child other than what is necessary for a child to participate in the activity. For instance, Company might ask for a parent's email address so Company can request information on how to send the child any prizes won or to tell a parent when his/her child has won a prize. 

Company also might collect contact information where it is necessary to protect a child's safety. 

A parent can always ask to review the information his/her child has submitted by sending an email to [webmaster@pizzahut.com](mailto:webmaster@pizzahut.com) or a written request addressed to Company, 14841 Dallas Parkway, Dallas, Texas 75254, Attention: Webmaster, Children's Online Privacy Act - Information Request, or by calling the webmaster at 972-338-7700. Requests must include the screen name of the child and any other information which will allow Company to verify that the requester is the parent of the child whose information is requested. A parent can ask to delete a child's information at any time and a parent can ask that Company not collect any more personal information from his/her child, by sending an email at [webmaster@pizzahut.com](mailto:webmaster@pizzahut.com) or a written request addressed to Company 14841 Dallas Parkway, Dallas, Texas 75254, Attn: Webmaster, Children's Online Privacy Act - Delete Request or by calling the Webmaster at 972-338-7700. 

## 

If you have any further questions concerning the Company's Privacy Policy and the use of your Personal Information, please contact [webmaster@pizzahut.com](mailto:webmaster@pizzahut.com). 

**Effective as of November 12, 2008**
